Guide to the Greentree Stud and Stable Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Greentree Stud and Stable records
1903-2000
MS 1953
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
42
(85 boxes)
The records document the organization and activities of Greentree Stud and Stable, a family-owned thoroughbred horse racing and breeding enterprise established by Helen Hay Whitney and Payne Whitney in the 1910s. The collection primarily consists of meeting minutes, reports, financial and legal records, correspondence, photographs, topical files, and newspaper clippings created or maintained by Greentree Stud and Stable. The records document many aspects of the organization, including its history, structure, and activities, primarily from the 1950s to its dissolution in 1994. Its horses, legal and financial activities, and dissolution are particularly well documented. The records provide a valuable resource on one of the most enduring and successful family thoroughbred racing and breeding operations in the United States.
Greentree Stud and Stable
Custodial History
Gift of the Greentree Foundation, 2009 and 2011.
Biographical / Historical
Greentree Stud and Stable (1910s-1994) was one of the most successful family thoroughbred racing and breeding stables in the United States. The original farm, Greentree Stables, was founded during the 1910s by Helen Hay Whitney, noted author and leader in the thoroughbred community, and her husband Payne Whitney, a prominent New York City financier. The establishment of the stable in Red Bank, New Jersey, continued the Whitney family tradition of thoroughbred horse racing and breeding begun by Payne Whitney's father, William C. Whitney, a founding member of the Jockey Club. At its height, the family's thoroughbred interests--collectively known as Greentree Stud and Stable--included horse training and breeding facilities in Red Bank, New Jersey (Greentree Stables); Lexington, Kentucky (Greentree Stud, a breeding center, and Mare's Nest Farm); Ocala, Florida (Ocala Farm); and Aiken, South Carolina (Greentree Stable, a training center).
The racing operations were primarily run by Helen Hay Whitney, while Payne Whitney focused on the breeding business. After her husband's death in 1927, Helen Hay Whitney managed all the operations until 1942. Her success in the field led to her being dubbed the "First Lady of Thoroughbred Racing." Citing the wartime economy as a precipitant, Helen Hay Whitney's children, John Hay Whitney and Joan Whitney Payson, partnered with their mother until her death in 1944. The partnership consolidated the three family members' racing and breeding operations, which included John Hay Whitney's Mare's Nest Farm and Joan Whitney Payson's Manhasset Stable (the name under which she raced). In the same year, John Hay Whitney changed the name of the business entity through which he managed his farm from Mare's Nest Stud, Inc., (formerly Llangollen Stable, Inc, 1932-1940) to Greentree Stud, Inc., to reflect the new arrangement. Both Joan Whitney Payson and John Hay Whitney were noted thoroughbred owners and breeders in their own right. John Hay Whitney owned Easter Hero, which was the first horse to win consecutive Cheltenham Gold Cups in 1929 and 1930. He was a founder of the American Thoroughbred Breeders' Association, a steward of the Jockey Club, and a racing commissioner in New York. He established Beckhampton, Ltd., to oversee his interest in English horse turf racing. Ownership of the stable was shared by two additional family members, Charles Shipman Payson (Joan's widower) from 1975 to 1980, and Betsey Cushing Whitney (John's wife) from 1980 to 1994.
When she began the stable, Helen Hay Whitney focused on steeplechase racing, but by the late 1920s she had switched focus to flat turf racing and breeding. The stable's breeding division produced 225 stakes winners. Thanks in part to the Whitney's breeding acumen and the talent of their longtime trainer John Gaver, Sr., the family's flat turf racing operations yielded several successful horses. Among their most notable horses were Twenty Grand, Shut Out, Devil Diver, Capot, Tom Fool and Stage Door Johnny. Twenty Grand won the Kentucky Derby and the Belmont Stakes in 1931, as did Shut Out in 1942. Capot won the 1949 Preakness and Belmont Stakes. Stage Door Johnny won the Belmont Stakes in 1968. Tom Fool won several major races from 1951 to 1953, earning him the title of United States Horse of the Year in 1953. In the 1930s and 1940s, Greentree was one of the most winning family stables in the nation. While never again matching the level of racing success the stable had in the first half of the century, it continued to have moderate success through the 1980s.
From 1944 to 1982, the business operations of the various farms were managed by Greentree Stud, Inc.; however, as sole shareholders the Whitneys were involved in most aspects of the operations including decisions to name, buy or sell horses, as well as to acquire and sell properties. By the 1980s, the family had sold farm properties in Florida, New Jersey, and New York. Following the death of John Hay Whitney in 1982, Betsey Cushing Whitney became sole owner of Greentree Stud and Stable. The transfer of ownership precipitated the dissolution of Greentree Stud, Inc., and the discontinuation of Beckhampton, Ltd. (the horse operations in the United Kingdom). Betsey Cushing Whitney formed an advisory committee to study and make recommendations for changes to Greentree Stud and Stable that would ensure profitability. She maintained operations for several years under the guidance of the advisory committee; however, the United States Tax Reform Act of 1986 made investing in horses less profitable than it had been in previous years. She gradually began to divest herself of horses, while retaining the main breeding facility in Lexington, Kentucky, and the training facility in Aiken, South Carolina. Betsey Cushing Whitney sold Greentree Stud (Lexington, Kentucky) in 1989 and Greentree Stable (Aiken, South Carolina) a year later. Betsey Cushing Whitney retained shares of several syndicates and owned several horses until she retired from racing and breeding in 1994, permanently retiring Greentree's racing colors (salmon pink and black striped sleeves with a black cap) at the same time.
Scope and Contents
The records, spanning the twentieth century, document the organization and activities of Greentree Stud and Stable, a network of Whitney family-owned thoroughbred horse racing and breeding farms. The collection primarily consists of meeting minutes, reports, financial and legal records, correspondence, photographs, topical files, and newspaper clippings created or maintained by Greentree Stud and Stable. The records document many aspects of the organization, including its history, structure, and activities, primarily from the 1950s to its dissolution in 1994.
Records pertaining to the history for the organization and activities before 1944 are few and primarily consist of appraisals of farms, reports on horses, photographs, a small amount of correspondence regarding Greentree Stud (on microfilm), and correspondence and publicity about Twenty Grand's Kentucky Derby win in 1931. The organization's post 1944 administration and financial history is more fully documented through meeting minutes, reports, financial statements, ledgers, and tax files. One of the collection's greatest strength is its documentation of Greentree Stud and Stable horses through farm and breeding reports, breeding records, genealogies, photographs, and publicity files. Also included in the collection are materials documenting John Hay Whitney's Llangollen Stable, Inc., and Mare's Nest Stud, Inc.
The records are organized in five series and one addition. The Correspondence files, are limited in scope but supplement the materials found in the Financial and Legal files and Topical files, which form the bulk of the records. The Financial and Legal files provide information about the organization's finances and assets, especially from the 1970s to 1994. Of particular note are the files relating to the sale of the last two farms in 1989 and 1990. Photographs primarily document Whitney-owned horses, but also include a few images of Helen Hay Whitney, farm employees, and the farms themselves. Reports and Meeting Minutes files are particularly valuable in tracing the organization's history. They include Llangollen Stable, Inc., Mare's Nest Stud, Inc., and Greentree Stud, Inc., stockholders' and directors' meeting minutes, as well as annual, farm, and breeding reports for Greentree Stud and Stable. The directors and advisory committee meeting minutes in particular provide documentation of, and insight into, decisions, activities, and evolution of the organization, including the merger of the Whitney horse operations in 1942 and its dissolution in 1994. In addition to the farm and breeding reports, the best documentation on the horses and breeding operations is found in the Topical files. The files include genealogies, inventories, syndicate files, and material on breeding, stallion services, and sales. Records pertaining to publicity and the racing associations and commissions are also included in the Topical files. Additional Materials include Advisory Committee meeting minutes, correspondence, and financial and legal files that provide a financial and legal picture of the organization under Betsey Cushing Whitney's stewardship from 1982 to the dissolution of Greentree Stud and Stable in 1994.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open to the Yale community for research and teaching. Other researchers require the written permission of the Greentree Foundation to access the collection prior to January 1, 2050, after which the papers are open for research without restriction.
Related Materials
John Hay Whitney and Betsey Cushing Whitney Family Papers (MS 1938). John Hay Whitney Foundation Records (MS 1952).
Arrangement
The papers are arranged in five series and one addition: I. Correspondence, 1920-1994. II. Financial and Legal, 1913-1994. III. Photographs, 1931-1986, undated. IV. Reports, 1932-1994. V. Topical, 1903-1995.
Horse Breeders -- United States; Horse racing; Horses -- Breeding -- United States; Race horses -- United States; Thoroughbred horse -- Breeding -- Florida; Thoroughbred horse -- Breeding -- Kentucky; Thoroughbred horse -- Breeding -- New Jersey; Thoroughbred horse -- Breeding -- New York; Thoroughbred horse -- Breeding -- South Carolina; Whitney, Betsey Cushing Roosevelt, 1908-1998; Whitney, Helen Hay, 1875-1944; Whitney, John Hay, 1904-1982; Greentree Stud and Stable
- Correspondence, 1920-1994; Series I
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically by correspondent or topic.
  - General, 1938-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - A-L, Inactive, Circa 1933-1957
    Scope and Contents
    Consists of microfilmed correspondence labeled "General Correspondence, Inactive to 1957." Only the first and last file names on each reel are provided. The bulk of the correspondence dates from the 1940s and 1950s.
    - Accounting balance sheets - Banks, U.S. Trust Company of New York valuations (Box 1a, Reel 1)
    - Bassett, James E., Jr. - Banks, First National Bank & Trust Company regarding Lexington, Kentucky (Box 1a, Reel 2)
    - First National Bank & Trust Company, Lexington, Kentucky - First National Bank of New York, general account (Box 1a, Reel 3)
    - First National Bank of New York - Greentree Thoroughbred, distribution reports (Box 1a, Reel 4)
    - Greentree Thoroughbred, general - Horses, foreign racings and breeding (Box 1a, Reel 5)
    - Horses, offers to purchase turned down - Insurance, autos, trucks and farm equipment (Box 1a, Reel 6)
    - Insurance, stud, horses - Insurance, liability and workmen's compensation (Box 1a, Reel 7)
    - Insurance, New York disability - Lexington, general (Box 1a, Reel 8)
    - Lexington, sales of tobacco, hay, water, sacks, etc. - Greentree Stud, Inc., valuations, portfolio summary (Box 1a, Reel 9)
  - American Horse Council, 1972-1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Arthur Andersen & Company, 1983-1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Balding, Gerald and Toby, 1956-1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Beard, Clarkson, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Beard, Louie, 1928-1945 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Boyd-Rochfort, Cecil, 1957-1961 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Breeding, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - British horse operations, 1962-1968 (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
  - Carter, Ledyard & Milburn, 1988-1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Congratulations (Twenty Grand's victory), 1931 June 13-14 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Contributions, 1976-1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Doughty, Tatyana, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Eclipse Award (John Hay Whitney), 1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Employees (termination), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Gaver, John M., Jr.
    - General, 1963-1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Termination, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Gaver, John M., Sr.
    - Employment contract, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
    - Horses, 1947-1967 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Includes correspondence with John Hay Whitney about the training status of various horses.
  - Grayson Foundation, 1979-1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Green, Robert, 1958-1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Horsemen's Benevolent and Protective Association, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Iroquois Realty Company, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Kentucky Heritage Commission, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Marketing, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Partnership, Greentree Stud and Stable, 1942-1945 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Pension plans, 1971-1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Portraits (horses)
    - General, 1979-1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Late Bloomer, 1979-1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Powers, W. L., 1920 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Sale, Greentree, 1988-1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Shearman & Sterling, 1982-1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stites & Harbison, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Stoll, Keenon & Park, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Syndicates, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Thoroughbred Breeders of Kentucky, Incorporated, 1967-1993 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Thoroughbred Publications, Incorporated, 1989-1993 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - United States Trust Company, 1982-1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Veterinary, 1982-1994 (Box 4, Folder 9-10)
  - Voting agreement, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Whitney, Betsey Cushing, 1986-1994 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Whitney, John Hay, 1947-1968 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Financial and Legal, 1913-1994; Series II
  The series is arranged by topic.
  - Financial
    - Accounting
      - General, 1975-1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Balance sheets, 1975-1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1976-1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Ledgers
        - Circa 1924-1930 (Box 6, Folder 1)
          Ledger titled, "Record of Races Won," consists of information on Easter Hero, Sir Lindsay, Slater, and Ferryside with winning values.
        - 1980-1982 (Greentree Stud) (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
        - 1982-1983 (Greentree Stable) (Box 8, Folder 1)
        - 1982-1984 (Greentree Stud) (Box 8, Folder 2)
        - 1983-1985 (Greentree Stud and Stable) (Box 9, Folder 1-4)
        - 1986-1988 Aug (Greentree Stud and Stable) (Box 10, Folder 1-4)
        - 1988 Sep-1990 (Greentree Stud and Stable) (Box 11, Folder 1-4)
        - 1990 (Greentree Stud) (Box 11, Folder 5-6)
        - 1991-1992 (Greentree Stud and Stable) (Box 12, Folder 1-3)
        - 1993-1994 (Greentree Stud and Stable) (Box 13, Folder 1-6)
        - Report maintenance, 1983-1991 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Quarterly payroll, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Reports, 1989-1994 (Box 14, Folder 3-4)
      - Stud fee
        - Expenses, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 5)
        - Income, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Auditing
      - Appraisals
        - Greentree Stud Farm, 1975-1978 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
        - Payson, Charles and Joan: rural estate, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Financial statements
        - 1942-1956/1957 (Box 16, Folder 1-16)
          Includes materials from Greentree Stud and Mare's Nest Farms.
        - 1957/1958-1978/1979 (Box 17, Folder 1-23)
        - 1979/1980-1989/1990 (Box 18, Folder 1-12)
      - Taxes
        - General, 1953-1970 (Box 18, Folder 13)
        - City
          - New Orleans, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 14)
          - New York City
            - General corporation tax, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 15-16)
            - Income tax, 1966-1972 (Box 18, Folder 17)
            - Unincorporated business tax, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 18)
        - Federal
          - General, 1984-1989 (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
          - Corporate income tax, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 3-5)
          - Tax preparation, 1990-1993 (Box 20, Folder 1-6)
          - Unemployment, 1984-1989 (Box 20, Folder 7)
        - State
          - General, 1960-1983 (Box 21, Folder 1)
          - Arkansas, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 2-3)
          - California
            - Corporate tax, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 4-5)
            - Qualification, 1968-1983 (Box 21, Folder 6)
            - Sales and use tax, 1967-1980 (Box 21, Folder 7)
          - Delaware, 1979-1981 (Box 21, Folder 8)
          - Florida
            - Corporate tax, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 9-10)
            - Qualification, 1960-1971 (Box 21, Folder 11)
            - Unemployment, 1983-1991 (Box 21, Folder 12)
          - Illinois, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 13-14)
          - Kentucky
            - General, 1989-1992 (Box 21, Folder 15)
            - Income and franchise, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
            - Labor department audit, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 3-4)
            - Qualification, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 5)
            - Sales and use tax
              - 1986-1990 (Box 23, Folder 1-5)
              - 1991-1993 (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
            - Use tax audit
              - General, 1985-1987 (Box 24, Folder 3)
              - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 4-5)
              - Returns and compliance forms
                - 1981-1983 (Box 24, Folder 6-8)
                - 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1-5)
                - 1986-1988 (Box 26, Folder 1-6)
          - Louisiana
            - Employment security law, 1970-1993 (Box 27, Folder 1)
            - Income and franchise, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 2-3)
            - Qualification, 1960-1981 (Box 27, Folder 4)
          - Maryland, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 5-6)
          - Massachusetts, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 7)
          - New Jersey
            - Business, 1945-1983 (Box 27, Folder 8)
            - Corporation tax, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 9-10)
            - Sales tax, 1945-1964 (Box 27, Folder 11)
          - New York
            - Corporate franchise tax, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
            - Income tax, 1982-1989 (Box 28, Folder 3)
            - Qualification, 1932 (Box 28, Folder 4)
            - Sales tax, 1982-1993 (Box 28, Folder 5)
            - Unemployment, 1982-1989 (Box 28, Folder 6)
          - South Carolina
            - Corporate tax, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 7-8)
            - Qualification, 1960-1964 (Box 28, Folder 9)
            - Survey, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Banking, 1984-1994
      - Authorized signers, 1982-1992 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - European-American Bank
        - General, 1986-1991 (Box 29, Folder 2)
        - Regular account, 1986-1991 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - First Security Bank
        - General, 1986-1990 (Box 29, Folder 4)
        - Regular account, 1986-1990 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - United States Trust Company
        - General account, 1992-1994 (Box 30, Folder 1-6)
        - Master account
          - 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 1-4)
          - 1986-1988 (Box 32, Folder 1-6)
          - 1989-1991 (Box 33, Folder 1-6)
    - Insurance, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
    - Sales
      - Greentree Stable (Aiken, South Carolina)
        - General, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 1)
        - Agreement correspondence, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 2)
        - Appraisals, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 3)
        - Broker's commission, receipt, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 4)
        - Contract of sale, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 5)
        - Escrow agreement, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 6)
        - Exclusive sales agency agreement, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 7)
        - Foreign Investment in Real Property Tax Act (FIRPTA) affidavit, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 8)
        - Gains tax affidavit, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 9)
        - Insurance binder, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 10)
        - Letter of intent, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 11)
        - Power of attorney, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 12)
        - Property survey, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 13)
        - Sale of Greentree Stables, Aiken, South Carolina, by Betsey Cushing Whitney to Marilynn Himes Riviere, 1990 September 14 (Box 35, Folder 14)
        - Title insurance policy, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Greentree Stud (Lexington, Kentucky)
        - General, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 1)
        - Accounting, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 2)
        - Commissions, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 3)
        - Contract, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 4)
        - Insurance, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 5)
        - Real estate taxes, 1987-1988 (Box 36, Folder 6)
        - Refunds, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 7)
        - Sale of Greentree Stud, Lexington, Kentucky by Betsey Cushing Whitney to Renwick Kentucky, Ltd., 1989 August 31 (Box 36, Folder 8)
        - Selling expenses, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 9)
        - Termination pay, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 10)
        - United Parcel Service, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 11)
        - Utility bills, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Ocala Annex (Ocala, Florida), 1969 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Legal
    - Appraisals
      Arranged chronologically.
      - Greentree Farm (Lexington, Kentucky), 1942 September 8 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Mare's Nest Farm (Lexington, Kentucky), 1942 September 8 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Estate of Helen Hay Whitney
        - Greentree Farm (New Jersey), 1944 September 24 (Box 37, Folder 2)
        - Real and Personal Property (Lexington, Kentucky), 1944 September 24 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Certificates, 1913, 1928, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Contract: Kentucky Utilities Company for rural line extension, 1949 December 12 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Deeds and leases
      - General, 1937-1949 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Aiken, South Carolina, 1964 June 15 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - [Lexington], Kentucky Deed for Highway Purposes, 1953 April 16 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Photographs, 1931-1986, undated; Series III
  The series is arranged by topic and alphabetically therein.
  - Horses
    Arranged alphabetically by horse name. Hyphenated names refer to the names of the mare and stud that bred the colt or foal. Includes portraits, snapshots, and action shots of horses, most of which were owned by the Whitneys.
    - Airy Going, 1937 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Amphitheatre, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Arctic Gold, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Armor Bearer, 1938-1939 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Arts and Letters, Circa 1969 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Astronomy First, Undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Audience, 1958-1960 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Badger Game, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Baltimore Chop, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Basket Weave (oversize), 1986 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Bimelech, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Bimlette, Circa 1946-1947 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Blandin-Cressida, 1934 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Blue Border, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Blue Eyed Momo, Circa 1946 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Bold Anna, Circa 1943 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Boomdeay, 1948, undated (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Bostonian-Kenya, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Bostonian-King's Fancy, Undated (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Bostonian-Maracaibo, Undated (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Braun Bud-Cressida, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Broomstick-Mad Hand, Undated (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Brud, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Bud Lerner-Aedana, Undated (Box 38, Folder 23)